<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>经济学人 on Uranus</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/tags/%E7%BB%8F%E6%B5%8E%E5%AD%A6%E4%BA%BA/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 经济学人 on Uranus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 13:12:19 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gotouranus.top/tags/%E7%BB%8F%E6%B5%8E%E5%AD%A6%E4%BA%BA/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week | 2020.03.26</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 13:12:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200330/</guid>
      <description>More countries rolled out wartime-like emergency measures to fight covid-19. In Britain people were told to leave home only in limited circumstances; gatherings of more than two people were banned. All non-essential businesses, pubs and restaurants were ordered to shut. The government announced an unprecedented aid package, including paying up to 80% of workers&amp;rsquo; wages. The American Congress prepared a $2trn economic-rescue bill, the biggest in modern history, which provides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese firms use obscure legal tactics to stem virus losses</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200225/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 20:31:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200225/</guid>
      <description>-- Chinese firms use obscure legal tactics to stem virus losses obscure 鲜为人知的 tactic [usually pl.] 策略，手段 stem : to stop sth that is flowing from spreading or increasing 阻止，封堵 &amp;ldquo;It is going to be an almighty legal mess for months and years to come.&amp;rdquo; That grim prognosis of the potential legal and business consequences of the viral</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy faces a sudden surge in covid-19 cases</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200224/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 20:31:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200224/</guid>
      <description>Italy faces a sudden surge in covid-19 cases surge （数量的）急剧上升 With disconcerting suddenness, Italy has found itself the European country worst affected by covid-19. By February 23rd the number of people infected with the coronavirus that first emerged in the Chinese city of Wuhan had leapt to 152, jump of around 100 within a day. Three of them all in their late</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>