<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>necrozizi</title>
    <link>https://necrozizi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on necrozizi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 20:31:49 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://necrozizi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese firms use obscure legal tactics to stem virus losses</title>
      <link>https://necrozizi.github.io/posts/20200225/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 20:31:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://necrozizi.github.io/posts/20200225/</guid>
      <description>Chinese firms use obscure legal tactics to stem virus losses  obscure  鲜为人知的   tactic  [usually pl.] 策略，手段   stem  : to stop sth that is flowing from spreading or increasing 阻止，封堵    &amp;ldquo;It is going to be an almighty legal mess for months and years to come.&amp;rdquo; That grim prognosis of the potential legal and business consequences of the viral outbreak in China comes from a veteran of the country&#39;s business scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy faces a sudden surge in covid-19 cases</title>
      <link>https://necrozizi.github.io/posts/20200224/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 20:31:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://necrozizi.github.io/posts/20200224/</guid>
      <description>Italy faces a sudden surge in covid-19 cases  surge：  With disconcerting suddenness, Italy has found itself the European country worst affected by covid-19. By February 23rd the number of people infected with the coronavirus that first emerged in the Chinese city of Wuhan had leapt to 152, jump of around 100 within a day. Three of them all in their late 60s or older, have already died. Italy now has the third-most cases in the world, after China itself, where 77,000 have been infected, and South Korea, where the total has surged to more than 600.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://necrozizi.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 20:31:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://necrozizi.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Heading 1 Heading 2  list list  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
