<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>æ‰€æœ‰æ–‡ç«  - Uranus</title>
        <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/</link>
        <description>æ‰€æœ‰æ–‡ç«  | Uranus</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:55:18 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.13) Part.03</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200616/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 23:55:18 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200616/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The Chinese city of Mudanjiang, on the border with Russia, became the second in the country, after Wuhan, to test all of its residents for coronavirus. Among the 780,000 people examined, at least 19 were found to be infected, without sysptoms. In April there had been a spike in cases in the city as Chinese citizens returned from Russia. resident å±…æ°‘ï¼Œä½æˆ· China warned its citizens to]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.13) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200615/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 10:24:09 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200615/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mali said it would investigate the army after men in uniform attacked two villages and killed 43 civilians in Mopti, in the centre of the country. The British government conceded that plans to return children to school in England were unworkable. After weeks of resistance from teachers and local authorities, barely half of the pupils in primary-year groups that could have gone back have done so. The return of pupils]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.13) Part.01</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200614/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 09:25:08 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200614/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Democrats in the House of Representatives introduced legislation to reform policing in America in the wake of the killing of George Floyd. The measures, which will be resisted in the Senate, would simplify the process for prosecuting officers for misconduct and curtail the &ldquo;qualified immunity&rdquo; law that shields them from civil lawsuits. Mr Floyd was laid to rest in his home town of Houston. Democrat ï¼ˆç¾Žå›½ï¼‰æ°‘]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Business this week (2020.06.06) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200613/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 20:44:47 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200613/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The euro zone&rsquo;s unemployment rate rose slightly in April to 7.3%. Almost 12m people were officially counted as jobless, far fewer than America&rsquo;s 23m. The British government announced that its scheme paying the wages of furloughed workers will end in October. In the final two months the government&rsquo;s contribution will drop from 80% to 60%; employers will have to cover 10% of the cost in September and 20% in October.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Business this week (2020.06.06) Part.01</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200610/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 12:56:03 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200610/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The Centre for Democracy and Technology, an internet-privacy watchdog, field the first lawsuit against Donald Trump&rsquo;s executive order seeking to strip social-media firms of liability protections for content posted on their platforms. The courts will probably rule eventually that the president does not have the authority to proclaim such a law, though federal agencies may try to implement it in the meantime. Mr Trump issued the order in a spat]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.06) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200608/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 12:41:57 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200608/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Bolivia&rsquo;s electoral tribunal agreed with political parties to hold a national election by September 6th. The vote will be a re-run of the one held in October, in which the president, Evo Morales, claimed victory but left office, and the country, after protesters accused him of electoral fraud. tribunal a type of court with the authority to deal with a particular problem or disagreement ç‰¹åˆ«æ³•åº­ï¼Œè£]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Etymology | -ium</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/ium/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 12:26:42 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/ium/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[-ium -ium ç”¨äºŽæž„æˆåŒ–å­¦ä¸­é‡‘å±žå…ƒç´ åç§°ã€‚åœ¨æ‹‰ä¸è¯­ä¸­æž„æˆé‡‘å±žåç§°ã€‚18ä¸–çºªæ™šæœŸï¼ŒåŒ–å­¦å®¶å¼€å§‹å…³æ³¨ç”¨è¡¨è¾¾åŒ–å­¦ç‰¹æ€§çš„è¯æ¥å‘½åç‰©è´¨ã€‚1811å¹´ï¼ŒBerzeli]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.06) Part. 01</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200606/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 21:52:05 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200606/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Both riots and peaceful protests spread across America in response to the death of George Floyd. It was the country&rsquo;s worst unrest for decades, prompting many states to call out the National Guard and cities to impose curfews. Looting accompanied the chaos; shops in midtown Manhattan were ransacked. The policeman who knelt on Mr Floyd&rsquo;s neck for nine minutes was indicted for second-degree murder; the three officers who failed to]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.05.30) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200601/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:26:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200601/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Electoral officials in Burundi declared the ruling party&rsquo;s candidate, Evariste Ndayishimiye, the winner in a presidential vote. Opposition parties say the election was rigged. Many dead people reportedly voted. electoral [only before noun] æœ‰å…³é€‰ä¸¾çš„ Burundi å¸ƒéš†è¿ªðŸ‡§ðŸ‡® rig ï¼ˆä»¥ä¸æ­£å½“çš„æ‰‹æ®µï¼‰æ“çºµï¼ŒæŽ§åˆ¶ More lockdown restrictions were eased in England. From mid-June, all shops]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.05.30) Part.01</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200531/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:28:48 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200531/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Protests erupted in Hong Kong after an announcement that the National People&rsquo;s Congress, China&rsquo;s rubber-stamp parliament, would impose a national-security law on the territory. The demonstrations were also fuelled by a proposal in the city&rsquo;s legislature to make insulting China&rsquo;s national anthem a crime. Mike Pompeo, America&rsquo;s secretary of state, said that the &ldquo;fact on the ground&rdquo; showed that Hong Kong was no longer autonomous. This could pave the way]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
