<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Uranus</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Uranus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 16:29:25 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.05.02) Part.01</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200502/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 16:29:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200502/</guid>
      <description>Spain announced a complicated four-phase, eight-week return to a &amp;ldquo;new normality&amp;rdquo;, which will vary in speed between provinces. If all goes well, Spaniards will be able to return to beaches and bars by the end of June, and in some places before then. France also outlined its own &amp;ldquo;deconfinement&amp;rdquo; strategy. Most businesses will be allowed to reopen from May 11th, except for cafés, restaurants and</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business this week (2020.04.25) Part.02</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200429/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 13:01:17 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200429/</guid>
      <description>Facebook invested $5.7bn in Jio Platforms, a telecoms and tech firm that is part of the Reliance Industries empire in India, giving it a stake of 10%. Over the past five years, 560m people in India have gained access to the internet. Facebook wants to tap that potential, noting the opportunity for connecting Jio&#39;s small-business service with WhatsApp so that shoppers can have &amp;ldquo;a seamless mobile experience&amp;rdquo;. telecoms [pl.] short</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business this week (2020.04.25) Part.01</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200428/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 08:45:42 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200428/</guid>
      <description>Oil prices tanked amid forecasts that demand will tumble this year. Brent crude dropped below $16.50 a barrel, a two-decade low. May contracts for West Texas Intermediate, the benchmark for American oil, fell into negative territory for the first time, plunging at one point to -$40 a barrel, meaning traders in effect paid for someone else to hold the commodity. Concern that storage facilities at a key delivery point were</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.25) Part.02</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200427/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 09:10:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200427/</guid>
      <description>After three elections in a year, Israel at last has a new government. Binyamin Netanyahu, the prime minister, made a deal with Benny Gantz, the former opposition leader, which will see Mr Netanyahu stay in office for 18 months. Then Mr Gantz will take over. Both men were under pressure to avoid another election and co-operate to tackle covid-19. under pressure 被迫 tackle to make a determined effort to</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.25) Part.01</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200425/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 11:04:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200425/</guid>
      <description>Brazil&#39;s president, Jair Bolsonaro, who has dismissed covid-19 as &amp;ldquo;sniffles&amp;quot;, spoke outside the army&#39;s headquarters at a rally against lockdowns. Some of the protesters called for a shutdown of Congress and the Supreme Court and urged the army to take control of the pandemic response. Mr Bolsonaro has said: &amp;ldquo;Really, I am the constitution.&amp;rdquo; He also sacked a health minister who supported lockdowns and replaced him with one who favours</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus briefs (2020.04.18)</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200424/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 14:59:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200424/</guid>
      <description>Boris Johnson was discharged from hospital, where he had been admitted to intensive care. The British prime minister is convalescing at Chequers, an official residence. discharge the act of officially allowing sb, or of telling sb, to leave somewhere, especially sb in a hospital or the army 获准离开；免职；出院；退伍 admit [often passive] (formal) 接收入院；收</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.18) Part.02</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200421/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 12:28:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200421/</guid>
      <description>Iraq&#39;s president nominated Mustafa al-Kadhimi, the intelligence chief, as prime minister. Mr Kadhimi is the third person tapped for the job since November, when Adel Abdul-Mahdi resigned under pressure from anti-government protests. The previous two nominees failed to win enough support in parliament to create a government. nominate 任命，指派 intelligence chief 情报主管 tap [usually passive] 委任，指定（某人</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.18) Part.01</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 17:11:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200420/</guid>
      <description>Donald Trump said that data suggested America was past the peak of the covid-19 outbreak, as he mooted guidelines to reopen the economy. The president created a council to look at the options, some of whose members were surprised to be included. Earlier he started a row with state governors who are trying to co-ordinate the lifting of some restrictions. He claimed they needed his permission; the constitution says they</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.04) Part.03</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200409/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 19:31:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200409/</guid>
      <description>Grasping an opportunity Hungary, which has been dismantling checks and balances on the executive for a decade, passed a covid-19 emergency law that gives Viktor Orban the power to rule by decree as prime minister. The opposition says the country has become a dictatorship. But the EU did not criticise Hungary by name, and the European People&#39;s Party, the EU-level group that includes Mr Orban&#39;s Fidesz party, made no move</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.04) Part.02</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200408/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 09:31:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200408/</guid>
      <description>A narco state America charged Venezuela&amp;lsquo;s dictator, Nicolás Maduro, and 14 other members of his regime with drug-trafficking, money-laundering and &amp;ldquo;narco-terrorism&amp;rdquo;. The State Department offered a reward of $15m for information leading to Mr Maduro&#39;s arrest. The indictments allege that he co-founded the &amp;ldquo;cartel of the suns&amp;rdquo;, which sought to flood America with cocaine. The State Department later said America would lift sanctions on</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.04.04) Part.01</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200407/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 10:31:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200407/</guid>
      <description>Scientists advising the American government about the covid-19 outbreak predicted that between 100,000 and 240,000 Americans could die, even with partial lockdowns and social-distancing measures in place. Donald Trump warned his compatriots &amp;ldquo;to be prepared for the hard days that lie ahead&amp;rdquo;. The United States now has more reported infections than any other country. New York city has recorded more deaths from the coronavirus than all but half a dozen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.03.26) Part.02</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200331/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 17:17:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200331/</guid>
      <description>The supreme leader of Iran, which is fighting one of the world&#39;s worst outbreaks of covid-19, rejected an offer of aid from America. &amp;ldquo;Possibly your medicine is a way to spread the virus more,&amp;rdquo; said Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, revealing an odd worldview. China&#39;s ambassador to America said it was &amp;ldquo;harmful&amp;rdquo; to speculate about the origin of covid-19. His remarks appeared aimed at a baseless conspiracy theory, promoted by some Chinese</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politics this week (2020.03.26) Part.01</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 17:14:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200330/</guid>
      <description>More countries rolled out wartime-like emergency measures to fight covid-19. In Britain people were told to leave home only in limited circumstances; gatherings of more than two people were banned. All non-essential businesses, pubs and restaurants were ordered to shut. The government announced an unprecedented aid package, including paying up to 80% of workers&amp;rsquo; wages. The American Congress prepared a $2trn economic-rescue bill, the biggest in modern history, which provides</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese firms use obscure legal tactics to stem virus losses</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200225/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:19:35 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200225/</guid>
      <description>Chinese firms use obscure legal tactics to stem virus losses obscure 鲜为人知的 tactic [usually pl.] 策略，手段 stem : to stop sth that is flowing from spreading or increasing 阻止，封堵 &amp;ldquo;It is going to be an almighty legal mess for months and years to come.&amp;rdquo; That grim prognosis of the potential legal and business consequences of the viral outbreak</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy faces a sudden surge in covid-19 cases</title>
      <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200224/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 17:19:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200224/</guid>
      <description>Italy faces a sudden surge in covid-19 cases surge （数量的）急剧上升 With disconcerting suddenness, Italy has found itself the European country worst affected by covid-19. By February 23rd the number of people infected with the coronavirus that first emerged in the Chinese city of Wuhan had leapt to 152, jump of around 100 within a day. Three of them all in their late</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>