<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>è‹±è¯­å­¦ä¹ è®°å½• - åˆ†ç±» - Uranus</title>
        <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/</link>
        <description>è‹±è¯­å­¦ä¹ è®°å½• - åˆ†ç±» - Uranus</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 12:41:57 &#43;0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.gotouranus.top/categories/%E8%8B%B1%E8%AF%AD%E5%AD%A6%E4%B9%A0%E8%AE%B0%E5%BD%95/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.06) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200608/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 12:41:57 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200608/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Bolivia&rsquo;s electoral tribunal agreed with political parties to hold a national election by September 6th. The vote will be a re-run of the one held in October, in which the president, Evo Morales, claimed victory but left office, and the country, after protesters accused him of electoral fraud. tribunal a type of court with the authority to deal with a particular problem or disagreement ç‰¹åˆ«æ³•åº­ï¼Œè£]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Etymology | -ium</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/ium/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 12:26:42 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/ium/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[-ium -ium ç”¨äºŽæž„æˆåŒ–å­¦ä¸­é‡‘å±žå…ƒç´ åç§°ã€‚åœ¨æ‹‰ä¸è¯­ä¸­æž„æˆé‡‘å±žåç§°ã€‚18ä¸–çºªæ™šæœŸï¼ŒåŒ–å­¦å®¶å¼€å§‹å…³æ³¨ç”¨è¡¨è¾¾åŒ–å­¦ç‰¹æ€§çš„è¯æ¥å‘½åç‰©è´¨ã€‚1811å¹´ï¼ŒBerzeli]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.06.06) Part. 01</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200606/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 21:52:05 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200606/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Both riots and peaceful protests spread across America in response to the death of George Floyd. It was the country&rsquo;s worst unrest for decades, prompting many states to call out the National Guard and cities to impose curfews. Looting accompanied the chaos; shops in midtown Manhattan were ransacked. The policeman who knelt on Mr Floyd&rsquo;s neck for nine minutes was indicted for second-degree murder; the three officers who failed to]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.05.30) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200601/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:26:41 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200601/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Electoral officials in Burundi declared the ruling party&rsquo;s candidate, Evariste Ndayishimiye, the winner in a presidential vote. Opposition parties say the election was rigged. Many dead people reportedly voted. electoral [only before noun] æœ‰å…³é€‰ä¸¾çš„ Burundi å¸ƒéš†è¿ªðŸ‡§ðŸ‡® rig ï¼ˆä»¥ä¸æ­£å½“çš„æ‰‹æ®µï¼‰æ“çºµï¼ŒæŽ§åˆ¶ More lockdown restrictions were eased in England. From mid-June, all shops]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.05.30) Part.01</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200531/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 09:28:48 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200531/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Protests erupted in Hong Kong after an announcement that the National People&rsquo;s Congress, China&rsquo;s rubber-stamp parliament, would impose a national-security law on the territory. The demonstrations were also fuelled by a proposal in the city&rsquo;s legislature to make insulting China&rsquo;s national anthem a crime. Mike Pompeo, America&rsquo;s secretary of state, said that the &ldquo;fact on the ground&rdquo; showed that Hong Kong was no longer autonomous. This could pave the way]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Solar&#39;s new power (Part.03)</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200529/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 11:09:21 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200529/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Not all perovskites are semiconductors. But a group based on a metal, such as tin, and a halogen, such as chlorine, bromine or iodine, do have that property. The ingredients of these metal-halide perovskites are, moreover, abundant and inexpensive. One of the leaders in the field of making cells out of them is Oxford PV, a British firm founded in 2010 to exploit work done on perovskites by Henry Snaith]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Solar&#39;s new power (Part.02)</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200528/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 09:42:59 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200528/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[One way to boost a cell&rsquo;s efficiency is to add layers tuned to different parts of the solar spectrum. This means reaching beyond silicon to other materials. So-called â…¢-â…¤ semiconductors, made of elements from group â…¢ of the periodic table (aluminium, gallium and indium) and group â…¤ (phosphorus and arsenic) are one approach. Indeed, gallium arsenide is already used in applications like satellites. John Geisz and his colleagues]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Solar&#39;s new power (Part.01)</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200527/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 09:42:16 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200527/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Solar energy has had a good crisis. In many parts of the world skies clear of pollution have helped photovoltaic power stations, which convert light into electricity, become more productive and reliable. Declining demand, meanwhile, has seen coal- and gas-fired stations taken offline. In Britain, on April 20th, solar generation peaked at 9.7 gigawatts. At the moment this happened that represented almost 30% of the country&rsquo;s electricity sup]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.05.23) Part.03</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200526/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:02:21 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200526/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The prime minister of Lesotho, Thomas Thabane, resigned after battling to stay in power despite claims he was involved in the murder of his ex-wife. Lesotho èŽ±ç´¢æ‰˜ðŸ‡±ðŸ‡¸ claim a statement that sth is true although it has not been proved and other people may not agree with or believe it å£°ç§° Nelson Teich quit as Brazil&rsquo;s health minister after just one month in the job.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Politics this week (2020.05.23) Part.02</title>
    <link>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200525/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 15:30:19 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>ä½œè€…</author>
    <guid>https://www.gotouranus.top/posts/20200525/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Marco Rubio took over as chairman of the Senate Intelligence Committee, when Richard Burr stepped down amid an FBI inquiry into claims he benefited from a briefing about the emerging covid-19 threat in mid-February by selling stock. Senate Intelligence Committee å‚è®®é™¢æƒ…æŠ¥å§”å‘˜ä¼š step down é€€ä½ briefing a meeting in which people are given instructions or information ä¼ è¾¾æŒ‡ç¤ºä¼šï¼›æƒ…]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
